Guide to the New York University Archives Biographical Files MC.317
New York University Archives
- Marcuvitz, Nathan, undated (Box 112)
- Marden, Orison S., undated (Box 112)
- Maret, Raymond, undated (Box 112)
- Margolin, Harold, undated (Box 112)
- Margolin, Leo J., undated (Box 112)
- Mariano Maria Rita, undated (Box 112)
- Marin, W. Peyton '29W, '31L, undated (Box 112)
- Marine, Joseph, undated (Box 112)
- Mark, Reuben, undated (Box 112)
- Marke, Julius, undated (Box 112)
- Markowitz, Arnold L., undated (Box 112)
- Markowski, Elizabeth M., undated (Box 112)
- Marks, Alvin M., undated (Box 112)
- Marks, Arthur '42W, '44D, undated (Box 112)
- Marks, Lillian, undated (Box 112)
- Markus, Marvin, undated (Box 112)
- Marquardt, William F., undated (Box 112)
- Marquet, Christine, undated (Box 112)
- Marra, Kim, undated (Box 112)
- Marrazzi, A.S., undated (Box 112)
- Marsel, Charles J., undated (Box 112)
- Marshak, Margo Post, undated (Box 112)
- Marshalik, Yevgeniy, undated (Box 112)
- Marshall, Charles, undated (Box 112)
- Marshall, Henry, undated (Box 112)
- Marshall, James, undated (Box 112)
- Marshall, Leona Dr., undated (Box 112)
- Marshall, Paule, undated (Box 112)
- Marsland, Douglas A., undated (Box 113)
- Marsocci, V.A., undated (Box 113)
- Martens, Joan F. '75, undated (Box 113)
- Martin, Anne, undated (Box 113)
- Martin, Barry, undated (Box 113)
- Martin, Benjamin N., undated (Box 113)
- Martin, Charlotte Helen, undated (Box 113)
- Martin, Clarence, undated (Box 113)
- Martin, W.R., undated (Box 113)
- Martin, Darnell, undated (Box 113)
- Martin, Jesse, undated (Box 113)
- Martin, Molly, undated (Box 113)
- Martin, Richard, undated (Box 113)
- Martin, Roger, undated (Box 113)
- Martin, Stan, undated (Box 113)
- Martins, Eric, undated (Box 113)
- Martucci, Josephine, undated (Box 113)
- Marx, Dorothy, undated (Box 113)
- Maslan, Frank, undated (Box 113)
- Mason, C., undated (Box 113)
- Mason, Cyrus, undated (Box 113)
- Mason, George Cotner, undated (Box 113)
- Mason, Grant, undated (Box 113)
- Mason, Gregory, undated (Box 113)
- Mason, Laurence G., undated (Box 113)
- Masson, Henry, undated (Box 113)
- Mast, Richard, undated (Box 113)
- Masterson, William Hoyle, undated (Box 113)
- Mateyko, Gladys, undated (Box 113)
- Matheny, Luke, undated (Box 113)
- Mathews, Cornelius, undated (Box 113)
- Mathews, James M., undated (Box 113)
- Mathis, Kenneth L., undated (Box 113)
- Mathwig, Gean M., undated (Box 113)
- Matsuda, Takechiyo, undated (Box 113)
- Maxwell, Jean, undated (Box 113)
- Matheney, Ruth V. (Dr.), undated (Box 113)
- Mathewson, Douglas, undated (Box 113)
- Mathis, Kenneth L., undated (Box 113)
- Matin, Leonard, undated (Box 113)
- Mattingly, Paul H., undated (Box 113)
- Mattlin, Howard B. Dr., undated (Box 113)
- Mauch, Gus, undated (Box 113)
- Maudel, Carol, undated (Box 113)
- Mauk, R. Lee, undated (Box 113)
- Mauriello, Joseph A., undated (Box 113)
- Mausner, Bernard, undated (Box 113)
- Mauss, Evelyn Abrams, undated (Box 113)
- Mayfield, Guy, undated (Box 113)
- Maxwell, Douglas F., undated (Box 113)
- Maxwell, Manuel, undated (Box 113)
- Maxwell, Dr. Margaret, undated (Box 113)
- Maxwell, Robert, undated (Box 113)
- May, Charles, undated (Box 113)
- May, William F., undated (Box 113)
- Maychick, Stella, undated (Box 113)
- Mayer, Michael, undated (Box 113)
- Mayer, Bernard '47Ed, undated (Box 113)
- Mayer, John '61E, undated (Box 113)
- Mayer, Donald S., undated (Box 113)
- Mayeri, Serena, undated (Box 113)
- Mayerson, Keith, undated (Box 113)
- Mayerson, Dr. Philip, undated (Box 113)
- Mayerson, Rose '65C, '67GBA, undated (Box 113)
- Mayes, Bernard, undated (Box 113)
- Mayfarth, Frances, undated (Box 113)
- Mayfield, Julian, undated (Box 113)
- Maysles, Albert, undated (Box 113)
- Mayzner, Mark S., undated (Box 113)
- Maze, Coleman L., undated (Box 114)
- Mazella, Donald P., undated (Box 114)
- Mazzara, Glenn, undated (Box 114)
- Mazer, William, undated (Box 114)
- Mazza, Thomas J., undated (Box 114)
- Mazzia, Valentina D.B., undated (Box 114)
- Mazzone-Clementi, Carlo, undated (Box 114)
- McAdam, E.L. Jr. - "Dr. Johnson and the King's Library" "the Johnsons Photographer", undated (Box 114)
- McCabe, John, undated (Box 114)
- McCaffrey, Carlyn Sandberg, undated (Box 114)
- McCall, H.W., undated (Box 114)
- McCarthy, Bill, undated (Box 114)
- McCarthy, Joseph, undated (Box 114)
- McCarthy, William V., undated (Box 114)
- McCaslin, Nellie, undated (Box 114)
- McCauley, John Corran Jr., undated (Box 114)
- McClain, Clinton, undated (Box 114)
- McClement, John H. Dr., undated (Box 114)
- McCloskey, Frank H., undated (Box 114)
- McClure, Richard D., undated (Box 114)
- McCollum, Dudley F., undated (Box 114)
- McCombs, Nelson, undated (Box 114)
- McConathy, Dale, undated (Box 114)
- McConn, Charles Maxwell, undated (Box 114)
- McConnell, D.W., undated (Box 114)
- McConnin, Robert A., undated (Box 114)
- McCormick, Monica, undated (Box 114)
- McCourt, Frank, undated (Box 114)
- McCoy, Eugene M., undated (Box 114)
- McCracken, Daniel D., undated (Box 114)
- McCray, Chirlane, 2015 (Box 192, Folder 29)
- McCready, Erna '21C, undated (Box 114)
- McCredie, James R., undated (Box 114)
- McCrone, Alistair W., undated (Box 114)
- McCrudden, Patti, undated (Box 114)
- McCullough, Bruce, undated (Box 114)
- McCratchen, Samuel, undated (Box 114)
- McDaniel, Paul R., undated (Box 114)
- McDarrah, Fred W., undated (Box 114)
- McDermott, Mike, undated (Box 114)
- McDermott, Robert S. '70L, undated (Box 114)
- McDonald, Heather, undated (Box 114)
- McDonald, Phillip B., undated (Box 114)
- McDonnell, Pamela, undated (Box 114)
- McEwen, Currier, undated (Box 115)
- McEwen, James, undated (Box 115)
- McGaughey, George L., undated (Box 115)
- McGee, Micki, undated (Box 115)
- McGhee, Paul Ansley, undated (Box 115)
- McGinnis, Thomas C., undated (Box 115)
- McGovern, George, undated (Box 115)
- McGowan, John J., undated (Box 115)
- McGrath, John J., undated (Box 115)
- McGraw, Harold, undated (Box 115)
- McGregor, Harvey, undated (Box 115)
- McGriff, Erline Perkins, undated (Box 115)
- McGuiness, Joyce Kidd, undated (Box 115)
- McGuire, Robert J. '62L, undated (Box 115)
- McIlwain, Charlton, undated (Box 115)
- McInnes, Russell, undated (Box 115)
- McIntyre, John, undated (Box 115)
- McIvers, William, undated (Box 115)
- McKay, Richard C., undated (Box 115)
- McKay, Robert B., undated (Box 115)
- McKean, Henry, undated (Box 115)
- McKee, Kenneth N., undated (Box 115)
- McKee, Wilbur K., undated (Box 115)
- McKee, William T, undated (Box 115)
- McKenna, John J. Dr., undated (Box 115)
- McKenna, Timothy, undated (Box 115)
- McKenzie, Allen Dean, undated (Box 115)
- McKenzie, Stan, undated (Box 115)
- McKeon, George, undated (Box 115)
- McKone, William, undated (Box 115)
- McKeon, William J., undated (Box 115)
- McLaughlin, Harold J., undated (Box 115)
- McLaughlin, David, undated (Box 115)
- McLaughlin, Samuel, undated (Box 115)
- McLean, Joseph E., undated (Box 116)
- McLelland, Ernestine B., undated (Box 116)
- McLeod, June, undated (Box 116)
- McLouth, Lawrence A., undated (Box 116)
- McMahon, Mary, undated (Box 116)
- McMahon, John C. Jr, undated (Box 116)
- McMahon, Michael, undated (Box 116)
- McMath, C.B. Jr., undated (Box 116)
- McMillan, Terry, undated (Box 116)
- McMullan, Patrick, undated (Box 116)
- McNamara, Brooks, undated (Box 116)
- McNeil, Robert E. Jr, undated (Box 116)
- McNeill, Lillian Mary, undated (Box 116)
- McNelis, Edward, undated (Box 116)
- McNichol, Kevin, undated (Box 116)
- McNiff, Alice Dr., undated (Box 116)
- McNulty, Frank, undated (Box 116)
- McNulty, Tom, undated (Box 116)
- McPherson, Gordon, undated (Box 116)
- McPoland, James, undated (Box 116)
- McQueen, David, undated (Box 116)
- McQueen, Steve, undated (Box 116)
- McReynolds, Robert A., undated (Box 116)
- McShane, J. Russell, Jr. '32A, undated (Box 116)
- McWhinney, Madeline, undated (Box 116)
- Mead, Lawrence, undated (Box 116)
- Mead, Lawrence M., undated (Box 116)
- Mead, Lawrence III, undated (Box 116)
- Mead, Margaret, undated (Box 116)
- Meagher, Sheila '55Ed, undated (Box 117)
- Mearns, Hughes, undated (Box 117)
- Mears, Ashley, undated (Box 117)
- Mecca, Anthony S. '27D, undated (Box 117)
- Mee, John F., undated (Box 117)
- Meehan, Chick, undated (Box 117)
- Meehan, John F., undated (Box 117)
- Meenaghan, Thomas M., undated (Box 117)
- Mehle, Roger W. '72 GBA, undated (Box 117)
- Mehr, Emanuel, undated (Box 117)
- Meinecke, Charlotte, undated (Box 117)
- Meinhardt, harold, undated (Box 117)
- Meisel, Perry, undated (Box 117)
- Meister, Herman C. Dr., undated (Box 117)
- Meister, Robert, undated (Box 117)
- Melamid, Alexandre, undated (Box 117)
- Melby, Ernest O., undated (Box 117)
- Melcher, Daniel, undated (Box 117)
- Mele, Deborah Marzo '79C, undated (Box 117)
- Mele, Sam, undated (Box 117)
- Meleny, Henry Edmund, undated (Box 117)
- Mellett, James, undated (Box 117)
- Meloy, Ada, undated (Box 117)
- Melnick, Edward, undated (Box 117)
- Meltzer, Daniel, undated (Box 117)
- Mendand, Louis (FAS), undated (Box 117)
- Mendel, Arthur P., undated (Box 117)
- Mendell, Rosalind B., undated (Box 117)
- Mendelson, Michael, undated (Box 117)
- Mendik, Bernard, undated (Box 117)
- Mendusa, Julie, undated (Box 117)
- Meng, Chih Dr., undated (Box 117)
- Mengel, Theodore H. Jr, undated (Box 117)
- Menn, Dr. Stuart J. '60A, '64M, undated (Box 117)
- Mentschikoff, Dr. Soia, undated (Box 117)
- Menzel, David, undated (Box 117)
- Menzel, Herbert Dr., undated (Box 117)
- Mercante, Arthur, undated (Box 118)
- Mercurio, Joseph, undated (Box 118)
- Mereness, Dorothy, undated (Box 118)
- Merino, Barbara D., undated (Box 118)
- Merkle, Edward A. '24C, undated (Box 118)
- Merola, Mario, undated (Box 118)
- Merolla, C.R. '57C, '62GBA, undated (Box 118)
- Meron, Theodor, undated (Box 118)
- Merriam, Eve, undated (Box 118)
- Merrick, John (GBA), undated (Box 118)
- Merritt, Arthur H., undated (Box 118)
- Merry, Sally Engle, undated (Box 118)
- Merry, Glenn, undated (Box 118)
- Merton, Vanessa, undated (Box 118)
- Mestel, Morris, undated (Box 118)
- Metcalfe, Tristram Walker, undated (Box 118)
- Meyer, Adolphe, undated (Box 118)
- Meyer, Carol H., undated (Box 118)
- Meyer, Charles, undated (Box 118)
- Meyer, Edwin Jr., undated (Box 118)
- Meyer, Andre, undated (Box 118)
- Meyer, Henry J. Jr, undated (Box 118)
- Meyer, Toni M. '71, undated (Box 118)
- Mayerowitz, Joel, undated (Box 118)
- Meyers, Alonzo, undated (Box 118)
- Meyers, Morton, undated (Box 118)
- Mezey, Mathy, undated (Box 118)
- Michael, Lloyd S. '41 Ed, undated (Box 118)
- Michalos, James, undated (Box 118)
- Michalowski, Roman, undated (Box 118)
- Michals, Debra, undated (Box 118)
- Michelson, Albert Abraham, undated (Box 118)
- Michelson, Annette (FAS), undated (Box 118)
- Michos, Constantino, undated (Box 118)
- Middleton, John F.M., undated (Box 118)
- Middendorf, Henry S. Jr, undated (Box 118)
- Middenford, II, William J. '54 GBA, undated (Box 118)
- Middlebrook, Leah Ruth, undated (Box 118)
- Midori, 1994, undated (Box 118)
- Mifflin, Margot, undated (Box 118)
- Mikhael, Mona (Near Eastern), undated (Box 118)
- Milgram, Anne, undated (Box 118)
- Millay, Edna St. Vincent, undated (Box 118)
- Millar, David, undated (Box 118)
- Miller, Carl F., undated (Box 118)
- Miller, Dr. Frederick, undated (Box 118)
- Miller, Edward Dr., undated (Box 118)
- Miller, Edwin, undated (Box 118)
- Miller, Eugene, undated (Box 118)
- Miller, Gabriel, undated (Box 118)
- Miller, Geoffrey P., undated (Box 118)
- Miller, George, undated (Box 118)
- Miller, Gifford, undated (Box 118)
- Miller, James E., undated (Box 118)
- Miller, James W., undated (Box 118)
- Miller, Jerome J., undated (Box 118)
- Miller, John (Bing), undated (Box 118)
- Miller, Franklin, undated (Box 118)
- Miller, Geoffrey, undated (Box 118)
- Miller, John G., undated (Box 118)
- Miller, Kenneth S., undated (Box 118)
- Miller, Lamar P., undated (Box 118)
- Miller, Lorraine, D. '48 W, '51 L, undated (Box 118)
- Miller, Marie-Chantal, undated (Box 119)
- Miller, Mark Crispin, undated (Box 119)
- Miller, Marshall, undated (Box 119)
- Miller, Maurice (SEHNAP), undated (Box 119)
- Miller, Michael, undated (Box 119)
- Miller, Oscar M., undated (Box 119)
- Miller, Richard H., undated (Box 119)
- Miller, Robert Ellis, undated (Box 119)
- Miller, Samuel, undated (Box 119)
- Miller, Spencer, undated (Box 119)
- Miller, Seymour W., undated (Box 119)
- Miller, Susan, undated (Box 119)
- Miller, Theodore C., undated (Box 119)
- Miller, Toby, undated (Box 119)
- Miller, Tor, undated (Box 119)
- Miller, Walter James, undated (Box 119)
- Miller, Walter R. Jr., undated (Box 119)
- Miller, William, undated (Box 119)
- Millett, Frederick J., undated (Box 119)
- Milligan, Robert L., undated (Box 119)
- Milliken, James B., undated (Box 119)
- Million, Elmer, undated (Box 119)
- Millman, David, undated (Box 119)
- Mills, Linda, undated (Box 119)
- Mills, Joshua, undated (Box 119)
- Milnor, James, undated (Box 119)
- Milstein, Paul, undated (Box 119)
- Milstein, Seymour, undated (Box 119)
- Minacci, Raymond L., undated (Box 119)
- Mincer, Allen (FAS), undated (Box 119)
- Minehan, Cathy, undated (Box 119)
- Minkoff, Nathaniel Mandel, undated (Box 119)
- Minor, Frances, undated (Box 119)
- Minot, Susan, undated (Box 119)
- Minskoff, Joseph, undated (Box 119)
- Minsky Sisters, undated (Box 119)
- Minter, Thomas K., undated (Box 119)
- Minturn, Lucy, undated (Box 119)
- Mintz, Elizabeth E., undated (Box 119)
- Mintz, Leonard, undated (Box 119)
- Mirabile, Thomas J. '27C, undated (Box 119)
- Mirabito, Paul S., undated (Box 119)
- Mirnan, Milton Jack, undated (Box 119)
- Miro, Joan, undated (Box 119)
- Mirsky, Chester L., undated (Box 119)
- Mischel, Walter, undated (Box 119)
- Mischler, Jacob, undated (Box 119)
- Mishne, Judith (SSW), undated (Box 119)
- Mishra, Bud, undated (Box 119)
- Mislow, Kurt Dr., undated (Box 119)
- Mitchell, Allan, undated (Box 119)
- Mitchell, Christopher, undated (Box 119)
- Mitchell, Don G., undated (Box 119)
- Mitchell, Fred, undated (Box 119)
- Mitchell, Henry, undated (Box 119)
- Mitchell, John Blair, undated (Box 119)
- Mitchell, Timothy, undated (Box 119)
- Mitchell, Yetta, undated (Box 119)
- Mitnick, Julie S. '72M, undated (Box 119)
- Mitsis, Philip T., undated (Box 119)
- Mitterrand, Francois, undated (Box 120)
- Mittleman, Jesse, undated (Box 120)
- Mitty, Dr. Virginia C., undated (Box 120)
- Mitty, Dr. William F. Jr, undated (Box 120)
- Mo, Hugh M. '73A, undated (Box 120)
- Modiano, Nancy, undated (Box 120)
- Modica, C. Daniel, undated (Box 120)
- Moe, Henry Allen, undated (Box 120)
- Mohammed, Khalid, undated (Box 120)
- Moir, Natalie Joffe, undated (Box 120)
- Moglia, Ronald, undated (Box 120)
- Mollin, Dr. Abraham D. '35D, undated (Box 120)
- Molloy, Sylvia, undated (Box 120)
- Molof, Alan H., undated (Box 120)
- Momma, Hal, undated (Box 120)
- Momplaisir, Francesca, undated (Box 120)
- Monaghan, Charles A., undated (Box 120)
- Monda, Antonio, undated (Box 120)
- Mondschein, Irving, undated (Box 120)
- Monges, Richard Gladwin, undated (Box 120)
- Monkofsky, Jerrold, undated (Box 120)
- Monroe, Kristin, undated (Box 120)
- Monroe, Leo L., undated (Box 120)
- Monson, Ingrid, undated (Box 120)
- Monson, Weldon P., undated (Box 120)
- Montalto, Mary Louise P. '78, '82, undated (Box 120)
- Montana, Patrick J., undated (Box 120)
- De Montebello, Philippe, undated (Box 120)
- Montello, Louise, undated (Box 120)
- Montgomery, Chandler, undated (Box 120)
- Montgomery, Velmanette, undated (Box 120)
- Mooney, James D., undated (Box 120)
- Moore, David (Gallatin), undated (Box 120)
- Moore, Dora J., undated (Box 120)
- Moore, Geoffrey, H., undated (Box 120)
- Moore, Rev. MSGR. Emerson '72 GPA, undated (Box 120)
- Moore, John S., undated (Box 120)
- Moore, Kermit, undated (Box 120)
- Moore, Vincent P. Jr '52C, undated (Box 120)
- Moorhead, John Joseph, undated (Box 120)
- Moor-Janowski, Jan, undated (Box 120)
- Moorman, Charlotte, undated (Box 120)
- Morales, Pablo A., undated (Box 120)
- Moran, Gabriel, undated (Box 120)
- Moran, Juliette '48G, undated (Box 120)
- Moran, Olin, undated (Box 120)
- Moran, Terrence, undated (Box 120)
- Morawetz, Nancy, undated (Box 120)
- Morawetz, Cathleen Synge, undated (Box 121)
- Mordkoff, Arnold M., undated (Box 121)
- Morelli, Odino Dr., undated (Box 121)
- Moreno, Anthony, undated (Box 121)
- Moreno, Frank, undated (Box 121)
- Moreno, Francisco Jose, undated (Box 121)
- Moreno, Jacob Levy, undated (Box 121)
- Morgenstern, Oskar, undated (Box 121)
- Moriarty, Thomas, undated (Box 121)
- Mork, Waldo H., undated (Box 121)
- Morris, Dick, undated (Box 121)
- Morris, Kenneth B., undated (Box 121)
- Morris, Kevin, undated (Box 121)
- Morris, Robert H., undated (Box 121)
- Morrison, Arthur H., Dr., undated (Box 121)
- Morrison, Phillip, undated (Box 121)
- Morrison, Robert T., undated (Box 121)
- Morrissey, Alice B., undated (Box 121)
- Morrow, Bruce, undated (Box 121)
- Morrow, Lester Coridon, undated (Box 121)
- Morrow, Phyllis, undated (Box 121)
- Morris, R.L., undated (Box 121)
- Morse, Samuel F.B., undated (Box 121)
- Morton, William Scott, undated (Box 121)
- Mosby, Katherine, undated (Box 121)
- Moses, L.G., undated (Box 121)
- Moses, Michael A., undated (Box 121)
- Moser, Edwin T., undated (Box 121)
- Moser, Jurgen, undated (Box 121)
- Moskowitz, Charles C., undated (Box 121)
- Movshon, J. Anthony, undated (Box 121)
- Moskowitz, Harvey D. Dr., undated (Box 122)
- Moskowitz, Jules, undated (Box 122)
- Mosley, Walter, undated (Box 122)
- Moss, Howard, undated (Box 122)
- Moss, Maximilian, undated (Box 122)
- Moss, Melvin, undated (Box 122)
- Moss, Mitchell, undated (Box 122)
- Moss, Dr. Stephen, undated (Box 122)
- Moss, Tobias, undated (Box 122)
- Most, Harry, undated (Box 122)
- Motley, Constance Baker '43W, undated (Box 122)
- Mott, Valentine, M.D., L.L.D. (1785-1865): "Memoir of", undated (Box 122)
- Mott, Valentine, Prof, undated (Box 122)
- Moultrie, H. Carl, undated (Box 122)
- Mount, Thomas Shepard, undated (Box 122)
- Mouquin, Henry, undated (Box 122)
- Mow, Van C. Dr., undated (Box 122)
- Moyers, Bill, undated (Box 122)
- Muhammad, Khallid, undated (Box 122)
- Mudge, William A., undated (Box 122)
- Muheim, Harry M., undated (Box 122)
- Mueler, Wheeler K., undated (Box 122)
- Mueller, Gerhard, undated (Box 122)
- Mueller, Rich, undated (Box 122)
- Muldowney, Mary H., undated (Box 122)
- Mulgrave, Dorothy I., undated (Box 122)
- Mulholland, Herbert, undated (Box 122)
- Mulholland, John H., undated (Box 122)
- Mullee, William R., undated (Box 122)
- Mullen, Thomas P., undated (Box 123)
- Muller, Peter '68A, undated (Box 123)
- Muller, Herbert J. Dr., undated (Box 123)
- Mulligan, James H., undated (Box 123)
- Mullish, Henry, undated (Box 123)
- Mulready, Patricia M., undated (Box 123)
- Mulreaney, Robert, undated (Box 123)
- Mulvihill, Elizabeth '83Ed, undated (Box 123)
- Mumma Jr, Dr. Richard D., undated (Box 123)
- Dunhall, Edgar J. '57 G., undated (Box 123)
- Munn, James Buell, undated (Box 123)
- Munitz, Milton, undated (Box 123)
- Musterman, Henry William, undated (Box 123)
- Muzio, Michael R., undated (Box 123)
- Munroe, J. Spencer, undated (Box 123)
- Muntz, Earl, undated (Box 123)
- Munues, Elizabeth Dr., undated (Box 123)
- Munzer, Margaret, undated (Box 123)
- Murdoch, Anna, undated (Box 123)
- Murillo-Rohde, Ildaura, undated (Box 123)
- Murphy, Colleen, undated (Box 123)
- Murphy, Edward, undated (Box 123)
- Murphy, George A., undated (Box 123)
- Murphy, George M., undated (Box 123)
- Murphy, Liam Beresford, undated (Box 123)
- Murphy, Mora, undated (Box 123)
- Murphy, Paul E., undated (Box 123)
- Murphy, Randall, undated (Box 123)
- Murphy, Thomas, undated (Box 123)
- Murray, Albert, undated (Box 123)
- Murr, Alfred Dr., undated (Box 123)
- Murray, Allen E., undated (Box 123)
- Murray, Ida E. '65G, undated (Box 123)
- Murray, James E., undated (Box 123)
- Murray, Roger F. '38GBA, '42GBA, undated (Box 123)
- Murray, Walter, undated (Box 123)
- Murray, William D., undated (Box 123)
- Murrin, Tom, undated (Box 123)
- Muskatbilt, Emanuel, undated (Box 123)
- Muschell, Charles '38Ed, undated (Box 123)
- Muschel, Herbert, undated (Box 123)
- Musser, John, undated (Box 123)
- Musser, Paul H., undated (Box 123)
- Myers, Alonzo F., undated (Box 123)
- Myers, George Henry, undated (Box 124)
- Myers, Hon Allen M. '34W, '37L, undated (Box 124)
- Myer, John, undated (Box 124)
- Myers, Walter, undated (Box 124)
- Mylin, E.E. (Hook), undated (Box 124)
- Myrick, Donald M., undated (Box 124)
- Myers, David, undated (Box 124)
- Myers, Fred, undated (Box 124)
- Myers, Patricia Hughes, undated (Box 124)
- Nachamkin, Boris '54C, undated (Box 124)
- Nadell, Edith L., undated (Box 124)
- Nadler, Jerrold, undated (Box 124)
- Nadler, Marcus, undated (Box 124)
- Nadler, Paul, undated (Box 124)
- Nagel, Bert, undated (Box 124)
- Nagle, Raymond J. (Dental), undated (Box 124)
- Nagle, Robin, undated (Box 124)
- Nagel, Thomas, undated (Box 124)
- Nagel, Thomas, undated (Box 124)
- Nadiri, Ishaq M., undated (Box 124)
- Nadler, Harvey, undated (Box 124)
- Nagel, Alexander C., undated (Box 124)
- Nagle, Robin, undated (Box 124)
- Nagy, Elsie R., undated (Box 124)
- Nagy, Ivan, undated (Box 124)
- Naiman, Doris, undated (Box 125)
- Naipaul, V.S., undated (Box 125)
- Nakiam, R., undated (Box 125)
- Nakian, Reuben, undated (Box 125)
- Nalbatian, Professor Haig R. '74W, undated (Box 125)
- Naor, Assaf, undated (Box 125)
- Nardiello, Dr. Vincent A. Jr., undated (Box 125)
- Nash, Abraham, undated (Box 125)
- Nash, Ben, undated (Box 125)
- Nash, Jay B., undated (Box 125)
- Nash, John B., undated (Box 125)
- Nash, Michael, undated (Box 125)
- Nateleu, Jr. Gerald E., undated (Box 125)
- Nathan, Alan, undated (Box 125)
- Nathan, Otto, undated (Box 125)
- Nathan, Seymour L., undated (Box 125)
- Nathans, Alan A., undated (Box 125)
- Nathanson, Lucile B., undated (Box 125)
- Natanson, Maurice, undated (Box 125)
- Mason, Arthur H., undated (Box 125)
- Naum, James, undated (Box 125)
- Naurath, Frank W., undated (Box 125)
- Nazarian, Robert H. CBPA '72, undated (Box 125)
- Nealon, Rita W., undated (Box 125)
- Neelankavil, James, undated (Box 125)
- Neff, Waiter, undated (Box 125)
- Neidhardt, Arnold, undated (Box 125)
- Neidle, Dr. Enid, undated (Box 125)
- Neipris, Janet, undated (Box 125)
- Nelkin, Dorothy, undated (Box 125)
- Nelkin, Dorothy, undated (Box 125)
- Nelligan, Gilbert J., undated (Box 125)
- Nelson, Arthur J., undated (Box 125)
- Nelson, Bonnie, undated (Box 126)
- Nelson, Diane Miele, undated (Box 126)
- Nelson, Norton, undated (Box 126)
- Nelson, Norton, undated (Box 126)
- Nelson, Richard, undated (Box 126)
- Nemethy, Peter, undated (Box 126)
- Nesci, Joe (Basketball Coach), undated (Box 126)
- Ness, Frederick, undated (Box 126)
- Nestle, Marion, undated (Box 126)
- Netzer, Dr. Dick, undated (Box 126)
- Netzer, Dick, undated (Box 126)
- Neuborne, Burt, undated (Box 126)
- Neuberg, Carl A., undated (Box 126)
- Neuburg, Hugo, undated (Box 126)
- Neufeld, Carolyn, undated (Box 126)
- Neumann, Paul S., undated (Box 126)
- Neuman, Joshua, undated (Box 126)
- Neuman, W. Russell, undated (Box 126)
- Neuman, Bertha and Irving, undated (Box 126)
- Neumann, Gerhard, undated (Box 126)
- Neustader, Arnold, undated (Box 126)
- Newbery, Donald A., undated (Box 126)
- Newberger, Varda, undated (Box 126)
- Nevwirth, Isaac, undated (Box 127)
- Newburger, Edward L., undated (Box 127)
- Newburger, Howard, undated (Box 127)
- Newkirk, Pamela, undated (Box 127)
- Newkirk, Pamela (Professor of Journalism), undated (Box 127)
- Newman, Allen T., undated (Box 127)
- Newman, Benjamin, undated (Box 127)
- Newman, Bernice, undated (Box 127)
- Newman, Bernard '28W, '29L, undated (Box 127)
- Newman, Howard Prof, undated (Box 127)
- Newman, Howard N., undated (Box 127)
- Newman, Kyle, undated (Box 127)
- Newman, J. Wilson, undated (Box 127)